University of Connecticut, Center for Oral History Interviews Collection 1984.0025
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
University of Connecticut, Center for Oral History Interviews Collection
undated, 1967 - 2014
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
1984.0025
32.5 Linear Feet
The collection contains transcripts of interviews conducted by the University of Connecticut Center for Oral History, and individuals and programs associated with the Center.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Acquisition Information
The initial transfer of materials took place in 1984. Subsequent projects have been transferred from the Center periodically and incorporated into the collection.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by project title. Each project is then organized alphabetically by the last name of the interviewee. Page counts for the transcripts are also listed (when available). The projects included in the collection are as follows:
American Association of University Professors (undated)
Bridgeport Socialists (undated)
Changing Landscape Through People: Connecticut Valley Tobacco (1982)
Chinese Urbanization and Urban Planning and American Studies in China (1985)
Colt Strike of 1934 (1981)
Conferences, Lectures, Etc. (1969-1993)
Connecticut Art Associations (1986)
Connecticut Communist Party (1986-1987)
Connecticut Credit Union League (1983-1984)
Connecticut General Assembly Oral History Project (1995-1997)
Connecticut Historical Society (1998)
Connecticut Workers and a Half Century of Technological Change, 1930-1980 (1981-1982)
Creating Connecticut's Modern General Assembly Oral History Project (1996-1997)
Foreign Interviews (1977-1978)
G. Fox & Co. (2006-2008)
Gravetending in the New Mansfield Cemetery (1997-1998)
The Greater Hartford Process (Coventry) (1972-1975)
Holocaust Survivors in the Connecticut Region (1980-1981)
Individual Oral Histories (1967-1989)
Italian Immigrant Gardens (1985-1987)
Last Drift: Connecticut's Last Commercial Windship Sailors (1987)
Living and Learning 1908-1983, 39 Woodland Street, Hartford (1982-1983)
Making of Urban History (1974-1992)
Manchester-Cheney Oral History Project (1971-1991)
Millworkers of Willimantic (1979-1980)
Nisei at UConn (2003)
Peoples of Connecticut (1973-1976)
Political Activities of the First Generation of Fully-Enfranchised Connecticut Women, 1920-1945 (1980-1982)
Red Brick in the Land of Steady Habits (125th anniversary history of the University) (2002-2004)
Southern New England Telephone Company (1999)
Student Projects (undated, 1981-1998)
Telling Our Stories: Women's Words/Women's Quilts (1991-1992)
Thomas Dodd Family Oral History Project (1976, 1995, 2009)
University of Connecticut (1968-2008)
Voices from the Second World War: An Oral History (1999-2000)
Voices of American Homemakers (1981-1985)
Witnesses to Nuremberg (circa 1997)
Women and the Connecticut Bar (undated)
Women in the Connecticut Legislature: Past and Present (1996-1997)
Women's Center Oral History Project (1997)
History
The Center was established as the Oral History Project in 1968 and began to expand in the late seventies in response to a growing professional interest in this research technique. It was designated a Center by the University's Board of Trustees in 1981; the Center's name was changed to the Oral History Office in 2007.
Center-based activities have been supported by funding from such agencies as the >National Endowment for the Humanities, the Connecticut Humanities Council and the U.S. Office of Education, as well as by private sources and the University of Connecticut.
Publications originating from the Center include: Mills and Meadows: A Pictorial History of Northeastern Connecticut, From the Old Country: An Oral History of European Migration to America, Connecticut Workers and Technological Change, and Witnesses to Nuremberg: American Participants at the War Crime Trials.
Custodial History
The recordings and transcripts were created by and housed in the Center for Oral History prior to their transfer to Archives & Special Collections. More recent projects undertaken by the Center and listed on their webpage are not available unless they are also listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content
The collection contains oral history transcripts recorded on reel to reel or cassette tapes. The media recordings, for the majority of the collection, are not available for research. The interviews were conducted by various individuals from the center, including Mortin Tenzer, Bruce Stave (Directors of the Center), Katya Williamson, Allice Hoffman, Jane Allison, Michael Chaney, and Leslie Frank.
Interviews included in this finding aid are limited to those for whom access permission has been granted. Associated, administrative, and project related files have been processed separately and identified as the University of Connecticut, Center for Oral History Records.
Sound recordings; Connecticut (state); Photocopies; Politicians; Labor; Audiocassettes; Ethnic groups; College teachers; Interviews; Oral histories (document genres); Holocaust survivors
- American Association of University Professors, undated (Box 1)
  General note
  [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Bruce M. Stave]
  - Curt Beck (35 pp.)
  - Judith Bridges (31 pp.)
  - Fred Cazel, (31 pp.)
  - Tony DiBenedetto (31pp.)
  - Joan Geetter (32 pp.)
  - Peter Halvorson (31 pp.)
  - Arnold Orza (45 pp.)
  - Charles A. Owen, Jr. (25 pp.)
  - Ed Purcell (28 pp.)
  - William "Bill" Rosen (36 pp.)
  - Morton Tenzer (76 pp.)
  - Walter Wardwell (32 pp.)
- Armenians in Connecticut, 2013-2014; 1984-0025/Armenians/ (Box Security Set--Armenians)
  Scope and Content Note
  Project undertaken and generously supported by the Norian Armenian Programs Committee (NAPC), University of Connecticut, in 2013. Interviews were conducted by Dr. Bruce M. Stave and Sondra Astor Stave.
  - Abalian, Lorina (21 pp.), 2013 October 10
  - Arzoomanian, Richard A. (28 pp.), 2013 December 1; 1988-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Arzoomanian
  - Ashekian, Julie (42 pp.), 2013 August 8; 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Ashekian
  - Bagdasarian, Ara (28 pp.), 2013 August 29; 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Bagdasarian
  - Bengoian, Dorothy (34 pp.), 2014 February 22; 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Bengoian
  - Brown, Adrianne (27 pp.), 2013 August 6; 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Brown
  - Garabedian, Jennie (40 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Garabedian
  - Geragosian, John C. (28 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Geragosian
  - Grigorian, Richard (28 pp.), 2014 January 28; 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Grigorian
  - Hartunian-Alumbaugh, Ruth (40 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Hartunian-Alumbaugh
  - Karanian, Agnes (25 pp.), 2014 February 17; 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Karanian
  - Mahakian, Ira (34 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Mahakian
  - Maljanian, Roxie G and Abrahamian, Mary S. (66 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Maljanian
  - Mazadoorian, Harry (43 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Mazadoorian
  - Nalbandian, Untzag [Father] (37 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Nalbandian
  - Sagherian, Malcolm J. (46 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Sagherian
  - Shahverdian, Arthur (37 pp.), 1984-0025/ArmenianAmericans/Shahverdian
  - Zeroogian-Wu, Noyem (37 pp.)
- Bridgeport Socialists, 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
  - Bergen, Jack (27 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
    Socialism; Interviews; Oral histories (document genres); University of Connecticut. Center for Oral History
  - Kunin, Jacob (13 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
    Oral histories (document genres); Interviews; Socialism; University of Connecticut. Center for Oral History
  - Lewis, Alfred Baker (Mr. and Mrs., 92pp.) [An interview with Alfred Baker Lewis by Rhoda Durkan, 1974 (28 pp.) is also included.], 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
    Socialism; Interviews; Oral histories (document genres)
  - Magner, Mary (15 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
    University of Connecticut. Center for Oral History
  - Parsons, Vida McLevy (18 pp. & 9 pp.) [edited interview], 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
    Oral histories (document genres); Interviews; Socialism; Connecticut (state); Bridgeport (inhabited place); University of Connecticut. Center for Oral History
  - Perrocco, Albert (25 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
    Oral histories (document genres); Interviews; Socialism; Bridgeport (inhabited place); Connecticut (state); University of Connecticut. Center for Oral History
  - Ribak, George (25 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
    Oral histories (document genres); Interviews; Bridgeport (inhabited place); Socialism; Connecticut (state); University of Connecticut. Center for Oral History
  - Shenton, John P. (31 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
  - Thomas, Norman (12 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesBgptSoc/Box3 (Box 3)
- Changing Landscape Through People: Connecticut Valley Tobacco, 1982 (Box 4)
  [Project Director: Katya Williamson. Interviews By: Katya Williamson; see also Connecticut Valley Tobacco Growers Association Records. An exhibit at the Old State House, Hartford, and a publication, Changing Landscape Through People: Connecticut Valley Tobacco, were produced in conjunction with this project.]
  - Carville, Jan (47 pp.), 1981 March; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Carville (Box 4, Folder 1 [39153013987757])
  - Dunn, Mulnite, Pelton, Waldron (45 pp.), Undated; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/GroupInterview_BD_EM_EP_SW (Box 4, Folder 2 [39153013987765])
  - Farrell, J. & Sheperd, Mrs. J.E. (13 pp.), Undated; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/GroupInterview_JF_JES (Box 4, Folder 3 [39153013987773])
  - Mulnite, Emil (60 pp.), 1982 July; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Mulnite (Box 4, Folder 4 [39153013987781])
  - Newfield, Richard (18 pp.), 1982 June; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Newfield (Box 4, Folder 5 [39153013987799])
  - Phillips, Wentworth (20 pp.), 1982 July; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Phillips (Box 4, Folder 6 [39153013987807])
  - Oscar Reese Family (14 pp.), 1981 November; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Reese (Box 4, Folder 7 [39153013987815])
  - Stoughton, L. Ellsworth (7 pp.), 1982 July; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Stoughton (Box 4, Folder 8 [39153013987823])
  - Szydlo, Henry (26 pp.), 1982 July; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Szydlo (Box 4, Folder 9 [39153013987831])
  - Taylor, Amos (10 pp.), 1982 July; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Taylor (Box 4, Folder 10 [39153013987849])
  - Woodford, Chester (20 pp.), 1982 July; 1984-0025/CTValleyTobacco/Woodford (Box 4, Folder 11 [39153013987856])
- Chinese Urbanization and Urban Planning and American Studies in China, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Chen, Charles (56 pp.), 1985 March 27; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Chen (Box 5, Folder 1 [39153013990199])
  - Bo, Feng-Cheng (23 pp.), 1985 March 14; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Bo (Box 5, Folder 2 [39153013990181])
  - Guan, Wei-Bin (24 pp.), 1985 April 20; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Guan (Box 5, Folder 3 [39153013990025])
  - Hou, Ren-Zhi (155 pp.), 1985 May 13; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Hou (Box 5, Folder 4 [39153013990017])
  - Institute of Tianjin (39 pp.), 1985 April 19; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Tianjin (Box 5, Folder 5 [39153013990173])
  - Li, Cheng Zou (27 pp.), 1985 January 22; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/LiCJ (Box 5, Folder 6 [39153013990165])
  - Liu, [Mr.] (14 pp.), 1985 February 1; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Liu (Box 5, Folder 7 [39153013990157])
  - Qi, Wenying (45 pp.), 1985 June 4; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Qi (Box 5, Folder 8 [39153013990009])
  - Wu, Liang-Yong (45 pp.), undated; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Wu (Box 5, Folder 9 [39153013989993])
  - Xu, Xueqiang (18 pp.), 1985 January 23; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Xu (Box 5, Folder 10 [39153013989985])
  - Yang, Wen Li (20 pp.), 1985 April 9, April 15; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Yang (Box 5, Folder 11 [39153013990140])
  - Yang, Sheng-Mao (28 pp.), 1985 April 18; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/YangSM (Box 5, Folder 12 [39153013989977])
  - Zhang, Bo (21 pp.), 1985 March 6, March 25; 1984-0025/SeriesChineseUrb/ZhangB (Box 5, Folder 13 [39153013990132])
  - Zhang, Ji Qian (27 pp.), 1985 April 2; 1984-0025/SeriesChineseUrb/ZhangJQ (Box 5, Folder 14 [39153013989969])
  - Zhang, Zhi-Hong (pp.), 1985 May 6; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/ZhangZH (Box 5, Folder 15 [39153013990124])
  - Zhou, Lei (49 pp.), 1985 January 4; 1984-0025/ChineseUrb/Zhou (Box 5, Folder 16 [39153013989951])
- Colt Strike of 1934, 1981 (Box 6)
  [Project Director: Alice Hoffman. Interviews By: Alice Hoffman>]
  - Cruikshank, Nelson (14 pp.), 1981 April 26; 1984-0025/ColtStrike/Cruikshank (Box 6, Folder 1 [39153013987708])
  - LaForge, Leo (29 pp.), 1981 April 26; 1984-0025/ColtStrike/LaForge (Box 6, Folder 2 [39153013987716])
  - Rourke (Joe), Cruikshank, et al. (18 pp.), 1980 March 14; 1984-0025/ColtStrike/GroupInterview_JR_NC_1 (Box 6, Folder 3 [39153013987724])
  - Rourke (Joe), Cruikshank, et al. (47 pp.), 1981 April 25; 1984-0025/ColtStrike/GroupInterview_JR_NC_2 (Box 6, Folder 4 [39153013987732])
  - St. Pierre, Euguene and Pauline Novak (30 pp.), 1981 April 27; 1984-0025/ColtStrike/GroupInterview_ES_PN (Box 6, Folder 5 [39153013987740])
- Conferences, Lectures, Etc., 1969-1993 (Box 7)
  - Connecticut Workers and Technological Change in the 1980's Conference (152 pp.), 1982; 1984-0025/ConferencesLectures/CTWorkersandTechChange (Box 7, Folder 1 [39153013989944], Folder 2 [39153013990108], Folder 3 [39153013989936], Folder 4 [39153013990090], Folder 5 [39153013989928], Folder 6 [39153013990082], Folder 7[ 39153013989910])
  - Holocaust Program (40 pp.), includes interviews with Ruth H. Klemens and Simon Konover, Holocaust survivors, 1992; 1984-0025/SeriesConferencesLectures/HolocaustKlemensKonover (Box 7, Folder 8 [39153013990074])
  - Holocaust Program (52 pp.), includes interviews with Henry Levy and Helen Kopman, Holocaust survivors, 1993; 1984-0025/SeriesConferencesLectures/HolocaustLevyKopman (Box 7, Folder 9 [39153013989902])
  - Elie Wiesel Convocation, 1988 September 7; 1984-0025/SeriesConferencesLectures/ConvocationWiesel (Box 7, Folder 10 [39153013990066])
- Connecticut Art Associations, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Stauffer, Ethel (22 pp.), 1986 March 25; 1984-0025/SeriesCTArtAssociations/Stauffer (Box 8, Folder 1 [39153013989886])
- Connecticut Communist Party, 1986-1987 (Box 9)
  General
  [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave, Jack Goldring. Interviews By: Bruce M. Stave, Jack Goldring
  - DeMaio, Ernest (93 pp.), 1987 July 14; 1984-0025/CTCommunistParty/DeMaio (Box 9, Folder 1 [39153013990041])
  - Goldring, Harriet (35 pp.), 1987 March 19; 1984-0025/CTCommunistParty/Goldring_H (Box 9, Folder 2 [39153013990355])
  - Goldring, Jack (110 pp./93 pp.), 1987 February 13, 27; 1984-0025/SeriesCTCommunistParty/Goldring_J (Box 9, Folder 3 [39153013990348], Folder 4 [39153013990330])
  - Goldring, Harriet and Jack (53 pp.), 1987 January 16; 1984-0025/CTCommunistParty/Goldring_HJ (Box 9, Folder 5 [39153013990322])
  - Hill, Larry (40 pp.), 1987 May 9; 1984-0025/SeriesCTCommunistParty/Hill (Box 9, Folder 6 [39153013990314])
  - Richter, Samuel (45 pp.), 1987 March 4; 1984-0025/SeriesCTCommunistParty/Richter (Box 9, Folder 7 [39153013990512])
  - Trudeau, Clyde (59 pp.), 1987 April 30; 1984-0025/SeriesCTCommunistParty/Trudeau (Box 9, Folder 8 [39153013990504])
- Connecticut Credit Union League, 1983-1984 (Box 10)
  [Project Director: Michael Chaney. Interviews By: Michael Chaney]
  - Beeny, George (40 pp.), 1984 May 29; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Beeny (Box 10, Folder 1 [39153013990488])
  - Bourland, Lawrence (30 pp.), 1984 March 2; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Bourland (Box 10, Folder 12 [39153013990470])
  - Curley, William (46 pp.), 1984 March 13; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Curley (Box 10, Folder 3 [39153013990306])
  - Curtiss, William (33 pp.), 1984 March 15; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Curtiss (Box 10, Folder 4 [39153013990462])
  - Douyard, Raymond (44 pp.), 1984 March 23; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Douyard (Box 10, Folder 5 [39153013990298])
  - Durkin, Thomas (53 pp.), 1984 February 3; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Durkin (Box 10, Folder 6 [39153013990454])
  - Edelson, Harry (35 pp.), 1984 March 9; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Edelson (Box 10, Folder 7 [39153013990447])
  - Fleury, Virginia (37 pp.), 1984 May 24; 1984-0025/SeriesCTCreditUnionLeague/Fleury (Box 10, Folder 8 [39153013990280])
  - Gilbert, James (34 pp.), 1984 May 21; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Gilbert (Box 10, Folder 9 [39153013990264])
  - Hoemann, Howard (48 pp.), 1984 April 27; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Hoemann (Box 10, Folder 10 [39153013990272])
  - Hutchinson, John (52 pp.), 1984 September 27; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Hutchinson (Box 10, Folder 11 [39153013990439])
  - Johnson, J. Arthur (30 pp.), 1984 May 25; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Johnson (Box 10, Folder 12 [39153013990421])
  - Knowlton, Lawrence A. (49 pp.), 1984 March 14; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Knowlton (Box 10, Folder 13 [39153013990256])
  - Labanara, Louis (29 pp.), 1984 March 15; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Labanara (Box 10, Folder 14 [39153013990413])
  - Labanara, Robert (19 pp.), 1984 April 27; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Labanara_R (Box 10, Folder 15 [39153013990405])
  - LeMay, Gerald J. (46 pp.), 1984 June 28; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Lemay (Box 10, Folder 16 [39153013990249])
  - Liucci, Michael (57 pp.), 1983 December 8; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Liucci (Box 10, Folder 17 [39153013990231])
  - Miroff, Franklin (43 pp.), 1984 March 13; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Miroff (Box 10, Folder 18 [39153013990223])
  - Olsson, O. Louis (36 pp.), 1984 February 17; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Olsson (Box 10, Folder 19 [39153013990215])
  - Tirinzoni, Joseph (38 pp.), 1984 May 31; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Tirinzoni (Box 10, Folder 20 [39153013990207])
  - Tong, Alfred (53 pp.), 1984 August 27; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Tong (Box 10, Folder 21 [39153013990397], Folder 22 [39153013990389])
  - Tuttle, Elmer (29 pp.), 1983 November 3; 1984-0025/CTCreditUnionLeague/Tuttle (Box 10, Folder 23 [39153013990371])
- Connecticut General Assembly Oral History Project, 1995 (Box 11)
  [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Bruce M. Stave. See also: Interviews listed under Creating Connecticut's Legislative Assembly and Student Projects (Lisbeth H. Dizney).]
  - 1995 Session
    - Bysiewicz, Susan [Representative] (24 pp.), 1984-0025/CTGeneralAssembly/Bysiewicz (Box 11, Folder 1 [39153013990520])
    - Dyson, William [Representative (34 pp.), 1984-0025/CTGeneralAssembly/Dyson (Box 11, Folder 2 [39153013990538])
    - Farr, Robert [Representative] (41 pp.), 1984-0025/CTGeneralAssembly/Farr (Box 11, Folder 3 [39153013990546])
    - Fleming, James [Senator] (39 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesCTGeneralAssembly/Fleming (Box 11, Folder 4 [39153013990686])
    - Genuario, Robert [Senator] (43 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesCTGeneralAssembly/Genuario (Box 11, Folder 5 [39153013990694])
    - Merrill, Denise [Representative] (60 pp.), 1984-0025/CTGeneralAssembly/Merrill (Box 11, Folder 6 [39153013990702])
    - O'Rourke, James [Representative] (40 pp.), 1984-0025/CTGeneralAssembly/ORourke (Box 11, Folder 7 [39153013990553])
    - Ritter, Thomas [Representative] (53 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesCTGeneralAssembly/Ritter (Box 11, Folder 8 [39153013990710])
    - Sullivan, Kevin [Senator] (48 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesCTGeneralAssembly/Sullivan (Box 11, Folder 9 [39153013990561])
    - Ward, Robert [Representative] (50 pp.), 1984-0025/SeriesCTGeneralAssembly/Ward (Box 11, Folder 10 [39153013990728])
- Connecticut Historical Society, 1998 (Box 12)
  [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave. Interviews By: Bruce M. Stave. NOTE: Copyright for this project is held by the Connecticut Historical Society. Copies of transcripts will be deposited at the Center for Oral History and made accessible through Archives & Special Collections in the Dodd Center.]
  - Abbe, Elizabeth (35 pp.), 1998 June 8; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Abbe (Box 12, Folder 1 [39153013990736])
  - Campbell, Hugh S. (26 pp.), 1998 June 10; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Campbell (Box 12, Folder 2 [39153013990587])
  - Collins, Atwood (32 pp.), 1998 June 12; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Collins (Box 12, Folder 3 [39153013990744])
  - Davis, John M. K. "Jack" (28 pp.), 1998 April 14; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Davis (Box 12, Folder 4 [39153013990595])
  - Edwards, Robert L. (26 pp.), 1998 October 8; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Edwards (Box 12, Folder 5 [39153013990751])
  - Engley, Donald B. (27 pp.), 1998 March 30; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Engley (Box 12, Folder 6 [39153013990603])
  - English, James F. (28 pp.), 1998 June 15; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/English (Box 12, Folder 7 [39153013990769])
  - Fox, Alison Barbour (15 pp.), 1998 July 6; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Fox (Box 12, Folder 8 [39153013990611])
  - Grant, Ellsworth (31 pp.), 1998 April 13; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Grant (Box 12, Folder 9 [39153013990777])
  - Holcombe, Shepherd (21 pp.), 1998 June 10; 1984-0025/SeriesCTHistoricalSociety/Holcombe (Box 12, Folder 10 [39153013990629])
  - Hoxie, Frances A. (46 pp.), 1998 March 30; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Hoxie (Box 12, Folder 11 [39153013990785])
  - Koda, Paul (47 pp.), 1998 June 8; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Koda (Box 12, Folder 12 [39153013990637])
  - Kugelman, Thomas (17 pp.), 1998 June 10; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Kugelman (Box 12, Folder 13 [39153013990793])
  - Lockwood, Boardman F. (26 pp.), 1988 March 10; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Lockwood (Box 12, Folder 14 [39153013990645])
  - Roberts, Kenneth DeWitt (15 pp.), 1998 May 28; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/Roberts (Box 12, Folder 15 [39153013990801])
  - Tilton, Charles, Sr. (13 pp.), 1998 June 16; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/TiltonSr. (Box 12, Folder 16 [39153013990652])
  - Tilton, Charles, Jr. (18 pp.), 1998 June 16; 1984-0025/CTHistoricalSociety/TiltonJr. (Box 12, Folder 17 [39153013990819])
- Connecticut Workers And A Half Century Of Technological Change, 1930-1980, 1981-1982
  [Project Director: Bruce M. Stave and Robert Asher. Interviews By: Various. Available on microform from Chadwick-Healy Publishing and in libraries around the country. Originally funded by a grant from the National Endowment for the Humanities>.]
  - Aldrich, Alton P. (31 pp.), 1981 October 22; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Aldrich (Box 14, Folder 1 [39153013987484])
  - Allvord, Omar (44 pp.), 1981 October 6; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Allvord (Box 14, Folder 2 [39153013987401])
  - Anderson, Ann (20 pp.), 1981 July 29; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Anderson (Box 14, Folder 3 [39153013987419])
  - Avallone, Frank (34 pp.), 1981 June 5; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Avallone (Box 14, Folder 4 [39153013987427])
  - Axon, James (24 pp.), 1982 June 8; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Axon (Box 14, Folder 5 [39153013987435])
  - Barbaret, Jules (26 pp.), 1981 June 16; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Barbaret_J (Box 14, Folder 6 [39153013987443])
  - Barbaret, Maurice (41 pp.), 1981 June 16; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Barbaret_M (Box 14, Folder 7 [39153013987450])
  - Bates, Matthew (28 pp.), 1981 November 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bates_M (Box 14, Folder 8 [39153013987468])
  - Bates, Pamela (25 pp.), 1981 November 2; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bates_P (Box 14, Folder 9 [39153013987476])
  - Baviello, Al (24 pp.), 1982 October 19; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Baviello (Box 14, Box-folder 10 [39153013987492])
  - Bednarz, Louis (21 pp.), 1981 July 7; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bednarz (Box 14, Folder 11 [39153013987500])
  - Bellico, Philip (17 pp.), 1982 August 8; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bellico (Box 14, Folder 12 [39153013987518])
  - Bibisi, Suzan (28 pp.), 1982 February 23; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bibisi (Box 14, Folder 13 [39153013987526])
  - Bilger, Michel (29 pp.), 1981 August 11; 1984-0025/CTWorkers/Bilger (Box 14, Folder 14 [39153013987534])